GERMÁN HORIANSKI

Buenos Aires, Argentina | germanhdev@gmail.com | +54 9 223 621 6726 | LinkedIn: in/ghorianski/ | Github: /GermanEH

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Full Stack Developer with one year of experience developing in React.js, Vue.js, y Node.js, among others. I successfully took part in tree group projects (two health-oriented, plus one e-commerce), two of which I led thanks to my ability to integrate the front-end with the back-end.

EXPERIENCE

14x – Survey, maintenance, and development of a retirement and pension management platform previously developed in Visual Basic and Microsoft SQL Server, belonging to the Pension Fund of a Profesional Association. Migration of it to Node.js and Vue.js. Julio 2023 to Enero 2023.

Tutor at Coder House - Advice on back-end programming courses (Node.js). In progress.

Lab manager - Inventory manager for laboratory equipment repair specialist. Stack: M.E.R.N.

GDx Solutions – Web scrapping application with automated and periodic execution in Google Cloud. Cloud Deployment of a Machine Learning algorithm. April to May 2023.

Stack: Puppeteer, NodeJs, Docker, y Google Cloud services (GC Build, GC Run, GC Container Registry, GC Schedule). I made a script that collects data from a government page to train a machine learning algorithm for predicting national energy demand. On the other hand, I extracted a Machine Learning Algorithm from a Google Colab, adapted its code in Python to deploy it in GC Cloud, and run it in an automated way at regular time intervals.

S.A.N.V.A. - "Binnacle" for information management of people's health (seven developers). April 2023.

Stack: React, Tailwind, Formik (front), Phyton and MongoDB (back).

Paranoid Bikes - E-commerce for selling bicycles (in React and Node.js). December 2022 to January 2023.

Stack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Express.js, Node.js, Redux, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, Firebase Google Auth, Stripe, Cloudinary, and React Hook Form. SCRUM methodology (3 sprints and final demo) with a team of 8 people. I coordinated the teams, and connected the back and front with Redux.

Pro-fy – Mobile App for hiring medical services (in React Native and Node.js). November 2022.

Stack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Express.js, Node.js, Redux, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, Firebase Google Auth, Stripe, Cloudinary, and React Hook Form. SCRUM methodology (3 sprints and final demo) with a team of 8 people. I coordinated the teams, and connected the back and front with Redux.

Paws and Claws - S.P.A. with general information on dog breeds (in React.js and Node.js). October 2022.

Stack: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Express.js, Node.js, Redux, Sequelize, PostgreSQL.

Features: Combined filters, sorting, pagination, search bar, product details and deletion, registration and login forms with validations, global state management, with Redux, routers, controllers, validators, and helpers, data-fetching from a third-party API, custom error-handling, normalized database (with models that have validators, constraints, and default values). Testing with Mocha and Chai.

[Previous experience]. Practicing lawyer. 2022.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Full Stack Developer | SoyHenry Bootcamp | Jul 2022 - Enero 2023.

• Intensive Bootcamp + 800 hours